<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<languages>

<!--FROM THIS FILE YOU CAN MODIFY THE LANGUAGES PRESENTED IN GAME-->

    <!--ENGLISH LANGUAGE-->
    <language name="English">
         <string name="title">Germ Game</string>
         <string name="play_game">Play Chutes and Ladders</string>
         <string name="options">Options</string>
         <string name="how_to_play">How To Play</string>
         <string name="instructions">
         Players take turns rolling dice to see how many squares to move.
         To end the game a player must land exactly on the final square.
         A player cannot move if he or she rolls past the final square.
         A player can advance upward if they land on the base of a palm tree.
         A player is set back if they land on the top of a mud slide.
         </string>
         <string name="back">Back</string>
         <string name="languages1">Languages</string>
         <string name="credits">Credits</string>
         <string name="num_players">Number Of Players</string>
         <string name="2players">2 Players</string>
         <string name="3players">3 Players</string>
         <string name="4players">4 Players</string>
         <string name="play">Play</string>
         <string name="ok">OK</string>
         <string name="player">Player</string>
         <string name="turn">Turn</string>
         <string name="wins">Wins!</string>
         <string name="resume">Resume</string>
         <string name="quit">Quit</string>
         <string name="roll">Roll</string>
         <string name="back_to_menu">Back To Menu</string>
         <string name="slide0">You ate food without washing your hands. Now you are sick.</string>
         <string name="slide1">You drank water without boiling or filtering. Oh no!</string>
         <string name="slide2">Scooping water with your hand spreads germs. Down, down, down.</string>
         <string name="slide3">You forgot to wash hands with soap after leaving the toilet. That will slow you down!</string>
         <string name="slide4">Drinking from a pond means drinking filth. A tummy ache slows you down.</string>
         <string name="slide5">Doing your business outside spreads filth.  Down the muddy slide!</string>
         <string name="ladder0">Wash hands with soap. Take a short cut.</string>
         <string name="ladder1">Filtered water keeps you healthy. Climb up that tree!</string>
         <string name="ladder2">Washing with soap after using the toilet. A fast way to Grandma’s!</string>
         <string name="ladder3">Using a toilet is a great idea. Take a short cut.</string>
         <string name="ladder4">Using a latrine is smart. Up you go!</string>
         <string name="ladder5">Drinking filtered water tastes good and is good for you. You are almost there!</string>
         <string name="music">Music</string>
         <string name="soundeffects">Sound Effects</string>
         <string name="rolled">Rolled</string>
    </language>

    <!--FRENCH LANGUAGE-->
    <language name="Français ">
         <string name="title">Germ Jeu</string>
         <string name="play_game">Jouer Chutes et échelles</string>
         <string name="options">Options</string>
         <string name="how_to_play">Comment jouer</string>
         <string name="instructions">
         Les joueurs se relayent pour voir le nombre de cases à déplacer.
         Pour terminer le jeu, un joueur doit atterrir exactement sur la dernière case.
         Un joueur ne peut pas bouger s'il passe la dernière case.
         Un joueur peut avancer vers le haut si elles atterrissent sur la base d'un palmier.
         Un joueur est reculé si elle atterrit sur le dessus d'un toboggan de boue.
         </string>
         <string name="back">Arrière</string>
         <string name="languages1">Langues</string>
         <string name="credits">Crédits</string>
         <string name="num_players">Nombre de joueurs</string>
         <string name="2players">2 Joueurs</string>
         <string name="3players">3 Joueurs</string>
         <string name="4players">4 Joueurs</string>
         <string name="play">Jouer</string>
         <string name="ok">D'accord</string>
         <string name="player">Joueur</string>
         <string name="turn">Tour</string>
         <string name="wins">Gagne!</string>
         <string name="resume">Reprendre</string>
         <string name="quit">Quitter</string>
         <string name="roll">Roulent</string>
         <string name="back_to_menu">Retour au menu</string>
         <string name="slide0">Vous avez mangé de la nourriture sans vous laver les mains. Maintenant, vous êtes malade.</string>
         <string name="slide1">Vous avez bu de l'eau sans bouillir ni filtrer. Oh non!</string>
         <string name="slide2">Récupérer de l'eau avec votre main répand les germes. Bas, bas, bas.</string>
         <string name="slide3">Vous avez oublié de vous laver les mains avec du savon après avoir quitté les toilettes. Cela vous ralentira!</string>
         <string name="slide4">Boire d'un étang signifie boire de la saleté. Un mal de ventre vous ralentit.</string>
         <string name="slide5">Faire votre entreprise à l'extérieur se répand la saleté. Descendez le toboggan boueux!</string>
         <string name="ladder0">Se laver les mains avec du savon. Prendre un raccourci.</string>
         <string name="ladder1">L'eau filtrée vous maintient en bonne santé. Monter cet arbre!</string>
         <string name="ladder2">Laver avec du savon après avoir utilisé les toilettes. Un moyen rapide pour Grandma's!</string>
         <string name="ladder3">Utiliser une toilette est une excellente idée. Prendre un raccourci.</string>
         <string name="ladder4">L'utilisation d'une latrine est intelligente. Up vous allez!</string>
         <string name="ladder5">Boire de l'eau filtrée goûte bon et est bon pour vous. Tu es presque là!</string>
         <string name="music">La Musique</string>
         <string name="soundeffects">Effets Sonores</string>
         <string name="rolled">Roulé</string>
    </language>

</languages>
